ED]
Today is the day of the Sakura Meets New Year's Party!
It's here, and it's about to start!
We have one day between events today.
I've got a lot of cameras going around and taking pictures.
That's what I'm talking about.
Thank you very much.
This is our first Sakura Meets Event.
Let's do our best to make it a success!
Let's do our best!
Let's go!
Hey!
Hey.
That's good.
It's so neat.
She's cute.
What?
Can I try it on Ena-san?
They're struggling, struggling.
If you do it this way...
Stick it like this.
Like this.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
Good, good, good.
That's it. That's it.
You got it.
You got it?
Let's do it again.
It's not what it looks like.
I got in trouble.
On the bus.
Oh.
That was quick.
What? - Sorry.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Takumi, is that your name?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
Sorry.
I can see you.
It's okay. It's okay.
Then stop.
Because it's really, really...
It's dangerous.
It's really dangerous.
Aio, stop it!
You're dangerous.
You're bad!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
OK.
Wow, this.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I want you to put it on properly.
A-ha-ha-ha-ha
Why are you putting it out?
A-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Just a minute.
ah-ha-ha-ha
here
a-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Oh, I'm scared.
A lot
My head
I feel like a wow.
It's been super fun, from the rehearsal.
I mean, there's a lot of stuff to set up, but...
I'm a little scared.
But when I'm doing the comedy
It's really fun.
I hope you can feel that atmosphere
I hope I can convey that atmosphere to you.
Hello. - Hello.
Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
How was rehearsal?
No, it wasn't perfect.
It wasn't perfect.
It's like 50% or something.
It's pretty packed.
From the customer's point of view.
Satisfaction.
If it's successful, it's going to be
I think it's going to be a high
I'm not sure yet.
I'm still a little bit
I'm not 100% done with everything yet.
I have a comic performance at noon.
In rehearsal, I'm going to do the last part.
I was like, "That's good, that's enough!
I don't know what you mean.
So I'll do my best.
Mr. Kawakami and Mr. Iwai might be able to see it.
My fan is expensive and dirty, so please don't shoot it!
Osaka often says my lunch box is dirty.
How is it? Is it good?
Delicious.
There's too much oil from the fried chicken.
Look at the seaweed.
But Matsuda-san said that since I talk a lot, it's important to keep my throat moist with oil.
I eat it before recording.
Mouth information
That's all.
Kiki and I are opposite, aren't we?
Onomoto-san wants me to show from the left and I want to show from the right, so we are in the worst possible condition.
I was surprised.
Don't tell me I'm cute.
It's impossible.
It's not impossible.
I am kerning paper.
More, more, more it's me and a bowl of rice.
I'm finally kerning paper too.
Can I play with kerning paper?
It's okay.
It's a good luck charm to look at at the worst possible time.
It's more like a bowl of rice with me.
I'll eat it.
I'll look for it and eat it.
It's more like a bowl of rice with me.
Baumkuchen.
Skipping one, it's baumkuchen, right?
Next time, I'll go to the store.
The first box I wrote on.
Here.
I want to serve it perfectly.
Oita cake.
I love it. It's Oita. Really.
Oita. I think I should go there.
Cake! God, cake!
Oh, no!
Wait a minute.
It's starting.
Oh, no! Help me! Help me!
Oh, no!
Help me, I think we're done here.
There, I think you're done
I'm going to the bathroom
I'm so nervous.
Have you ever done that in front of an audience?
Live music.
That kind of thing.
You know, the usual buddies come in.
In a live show...
As an idol
As idols.
But as an idol, you're so cool.
Say it, say it, say it.
I'm just trying to make them laugh.
I'm not there yet.
I haven't been able to...
I don't think I've been able to do it for many people.
I think.
That's why I'm here today.
In that sense, today
In the sense that I want to bring laughter to everyone
I've received so many
I got a lot of laughs.
I hope we can do it without asking.
I hope we can do it.
Thank you. I'm sorry. I'm leaving.
Today.
Sakurahama.
Today's Sakurahama.
It's an event.
Night water, night water.
water water water
Really.
Maybe.
Sakura-sui members
I know it's a lot to remember.
I'm sure it's a lot of work.
But it's a lot less than that.
I'm just trying to have fun.
I'm really just trying to have fun.
That's right.
But I remembered something that sounded really hard.
Well, it was amazing.
Rehearsal looked funny.
They were just laughing like normal people.
I want to go see it.
I think you'd enjoy it.
That's great, because the four of you worked so hard.
It's a good feeling.
It was nice.
It's nice.
Oh, please.
Are we all going next time?
Yes, for sure.
But I'd love to.
Really?
I did my best to get there.
I'm on my way home.
Please come back as soon as you can.
I'm a little nervous about leaving first.
What do you mean, "ah-hi-yoo"?
I don't know.
It's a natural gesture.
I knew it.
Look at the new kerning paper.
It's gone!
Gone!
It's a circle, but it's smeared.
It's the best paper I've ever seen.
You said thank you when we decided to do it.
He's not here.
It's from Mitsutake, who's not here
From Mitsutake, who's not here...
It's not the same today, is it?
It's better if you ask me to dance. I can still dance.
No, it's not.
Happy New Year!
I am Rina Inoue of Sakurazaka 46.
I'm Kiho Onuma.
I am Yui Takemoto.
I am Kera Masumoto.
Today, we are going to have "Gather! Sakura Meets New Year Party,
Thank you very much for coming to Hill Meets.
You all still have your first laugh, don't you?
Huh? I don't know why it's so subtle.
I can't hear your voice.
Terada-san.
He might be here.
Tanaka's...
Tanaka-san.
Please come again.
Are you getting a lot of laughs from the fathers?
Cheat sheet is available
Alcohol Week
Mr. Onuma is doing it too!
Mr. Onuma is doing a cheat sheet too!
Eh, but is it long enough, that boy
I wonder if it should be this big
Fathers are posting their cheat sheets
Comps are January 1st, 12th, 12th
Comps are comps
It's like this, right?
Boom!
Boom in the other room!
I don't know how to dance.
Socks?
I know what you're talking about.
You're not making me laugh.
I've switched sides.
I've changed my depression.
I've changed my depression
Can Kai Challenge!
Yay!
If you succeed...
We all fail.
Yeah!
Come on, come on.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Ha-ha-ha, Anu.
I'm not returning your money tonight.
Three minutes ago. I'll give it back on the last train.
I'll return it on the last train. I'll return it on the last train.
It's okay, right? Is that right?
Is that a good idea? Yes, it is.
The night view was great. The night view was a lot of fun, though, wasn't it?
That's great.
I'm so excited.
Are your ears a little too perky? Yes, I'm sure.
I'm totally fine.
Puddin'! Puddin', come here!
Puddin'!
Hello! Hello!
Hello!
Let me start by giving you the lowdown on what's going on.
First of all, everyone in this room.
Please sit down with the person who won the rock-paper-scissors game.
And no partner.
No partner.
When the number of participants has decreased to a certain extent...
Hira-chan, the last boss, and
Rock, paper, scissors.
Why?
I'm a bit of a stickler.
I want to do it.
The last boss?
Just when you think you've got it.
When we're down to a small group.
I'll have them fight the last boss.
That's good.
It was a little weird.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Oh, I like that one.
What do you say?
This is Poland, where you can participate.
That's weird.
He's doing something, isn't he?
Before the glitter.
I'm going to let the sparkles through.
That's right.
I put the sparkles through the glitter.
I let the sparkles through.
If you guys cheat, it'll be on the feed.
It's easy to get caught.
I'll make sure of it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, my God.
You've grown up.
A little bit.
You're breathing so well.
Yeah, I wonder if I've got the right name.
I don't know. I don't know if I'm going to get mad.
Okay, that's enough.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Well, seriously.
I didn't expect to hear you laugh.
You screamed.
Oh, my God.
You said it was a whole world of girls.
Scary.
So have a high tension
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Why not?
So you can see this?
Yes, ma'am.
We're done.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen.
It was great.
It was a lot of fun.
That was awesome.
We did it all!
I can't believe it's been a year.
I was looking at the cherry blossoms when it started.
I remember the shock.
I was so happy.
I almost cried at the opening.
I was about to cry.
After that, we had a lot of comedians come to the stage every week.
I think we were able to put everything we've learned to the test on this stage.
We've done almost all of the Hatewell debuts differently.
It's also completely different.
We put a lot of thought into it.
We did a lot of filming.
And we all bonded again that day.
We were saved.
Wisdom.
Chie
We will do our best again in the future.
Please continue to support Mitsu.
Thank you very much.